This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Unable to save Ace's life during the War of the Best,
the injured Luffy was taken to Amazon Lily,
where he fell into despair.
But this is a story from ten years ago in the East Blue.
Ace, Sabo, and Luffy finally beat the tiger with Nagari's guidance,
then bid him farewell as he continued his own voyage.
Freedom Taken Away! The Nobles' Plot Closing In on the Brothers!
Hold on tight! The storm's starting to pick up!
It better be! I'm bored! This is nothing!
Hey! Guys! It keeps getting windier and windier!
Loopy, you better not let go of that flag!
Real pirates can't have a whipping storm blow their flag away!
Gotcha! Come on, stupid storm!
You're gonna have to do better than that!
Yeah! Come on, bring it!
Get ready, cause here we go!
Crap! Loopy!
You okay?
Do I look okay to you?
Actually, yeah, it looks fun!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
We didn't get blown away or nothing!
That was cool!
Yeah, too bad we gotta build a new hideout, though.
No biggie. We just gotta grab some new parts.
This time, I want a big ol' telescope!
You'll never find something that nice here, stupid!
Ugh, I think I'd rather have a cannon.
Maybe some dummy threw one away!
Lame, I think you were right!
I haven't found anything like a telescope anywhere!
Shut up!
We didn't come out here to get you a worthless telescope!
Go find something useful!
Not much for planks, but I can always use another pipe.
It's a telescope!
Luffy's not gonna believe this!
Well, hello there.
Who would've thought one of the three great terminal brats was from a noble family?
Oh, yeah?
And who told you that, huh?
All right, men. Try not to leave a mark.
You jerks want a piece of me! Come on!
Oh, wow! Nice shot!
You ready to take them on, Sabo?
Yeah!
Nobody can take on all three of us at once.
I don't care if they are pirates.
That's right! We beat that big ol' tiger, so you guys are nothing!
Yeah? Just try me!
I know how we can wrap this one up fast!
Let's go straight for the captain!
Yeah!
Ah!
All right, kiddos. Just give up nice and easy.
We never give up, you hear me?
Ah!
Let go!
What do you want?
Get off my head!
I'm gonna go go go!
Yeah!
Leave us alone!
Ugh!
It appears I arrived just in time.
Crap, it's my dad!
He's gone, and we didn't harm a hair on his noble head.
Bring him.
Don't you dare!
Hey, no!
He wanted to find me so bad he hired pirates?
Those other boys, they're the ones who tempted Sabo into a life of debauchery and wickedness.
Give him back, you jerk!
What do you mean, give him back, you filthy rat?
Sabo is my son, which means that he's obligated to live on the path that I have prepared for him.
You should be ashamed.
You should be ashamed, steering him toward the life of a petty thief.
You're both nothing but wannabe thugs.
Why did you do it?
For my money?
Screw your damn money!
Ah!
You foolish pirate!
Quit knocking that kid around so carelessly!
You'll get that delinquent's disgusting blood on my nice clothes!
Hey!
Come back here!
Stop this, okay?
Nobody tempted me to do anything!
I only ran away because I wanted to!
I'll be dealing with you later, Sabo!
Take him!
Deal with the other two however you see fit!
Not a problem, sir.
You've already paid us quite handsomely.
We'll make sure these two never bother your boy again.
I'll spare you the gory details.
Wait!
Blue Jam!
Please don't hurt them!
Call them off, Dad!
I get it!
Please stop!
Huh?
What do you mean you get it?
Don't you dare, Sabo!
I'll do whatever you want me to, okay?
I'll live whatever life you've mapped out!
Just please!
I'm begging you!
Don't hurt my friends!
They've done nothing wrong!
I can't stand this!
Those two are my brothers!
Sabo, no!
Oh?
If that's what you want, then go home!
And promise you'll stop playing pirate with Lolice in this trash heap!
No!
Don't do it!
Shut up, kid!
Damn it, Sabo!
Run away from them!
Luffy and I can take care of ourselves!
This is your life!
You have to be free!
He's right!
Don't go!
Are you gonna abandon all your dreams just like that?
Sabo!
Hey, Captain.
What do you want us to do with the other ones?
We'll take them back to the hideout.
Yes, sir.
Bastard!
Untie me!
Come here and fight!
I'm not gonna lose this time!
Shut your mouth, brat!
Why'd you bring us to your hideout?
You should've just killed us!
It must be awful nice to be a noble.
Wouldn't you punks agree?
To them, we're no different than the piles of garbage we live in.
They just sit back while we do all the dirty work.
It's a pretty cushy life your buddy's living, I'd say.
You got no clue what you're talking about!
Pirate life is way better than being a stupid noble!
Sabo!
So himself!
You kids are so hopeless.
I can't help feeling bad for you.
Hey!
Untie their robes in quick!
Yes, sir.
Why do you think a kid from a noble family ran off to a place like Grey Terminal?
Did you think he just wanted to make some new friends?
He was mocking you and all the other people here, just like adult nobles do when they're
feeling bored.
Real sorry to break it to you that boy's no friend of yours.
You're lying!
Sabo would never pull a stunt like that!
He's right!
We were brothers, you heard him!
Yeah, guess so. Whatever you kids say.
But in any case, you boys aren't gonna bother him or his family anymore, are you?
Cause if that's the plan, I'm afraid I'd have to take you both out right here and now.
If you really think of him as your brother, it'd be best for everyone to leave him alone.
Leave him alone? What about our dream?
No! Sabo told us that he hates Hightown!
Look, if you really care about this Sabo kid, then you gotta let him go live his own life.
You'll understand when you grow up.
Anyway, until recently I had a bone to pick with you after what happened with Porchemy and our money.
But I'm over all that now.
In fact, I'm kind of impressed at how tough you little punks are.
Which is why I wanted to ask you something.
It might just be worth your while.
Thanks to you boys, I'm kinda short-handed.
So, how would you feel about doing a job for me?
Don't worry, it's a short, easy gig.
There's actually not really much danger involved.
On that barrel's a map of Grey Terminal.
You just have to carry packages to the locations marked on the map with an X.
You interested?
Okay, sure.
What about pay?
My head is tired.
Pulling stuff's no fun if Sabo's not around.
Just deal with it.
I don't like this either.
I'd much rather find Sabo and rescue him.
But Blue Jam had a point.
We've gotta let him live his own life.
Look, give it some time.
He's gonna be alright.
And if he doesn't like it, he can always come and join us again.
Until that happens, let's keep putting money in the pirate fund.
Believe what you want, it's still not Ace and Luffy's fault.
Quit wasting our time.
Tell us the truth.
Wait just a minute.
Those scoundrels must have threatened you.
They really have you wrapped around their fingers.
No, they aren't those kind of people, okay?
Any noble with a criminal record to his name will damage his family's hard-earned reputation.
You would also be barred from entering Hightown.
Those two forced you to leave home and get involved with their atrocious acts of violence against your better judgment.
Isn't that right, Sabo?
Look here, son.
The fate of your friends in Grey Terminal is in the hand of pirates.
Those pirates work for me.
All I need to do is give the order.
If these slum brats are that important, think long and hard about what you have to do.
You're a smart boy, born to a great family.
You already know what's right.
You promised me you wouldn't hurt them.
That's the only reason I came back here.
You haven't changed at all since I ran away.
No one tempted me.
I made every decision by my own free will.
You disappoint me.
I apologize, sir.
I'm so ashamed that I have such a foolish son.
Surely you understand my dilemma.
Of course.
It must tear you apart inside.
Don't you worry.
I'll take care of all the paperwork.
Welcome back, sir.
Home at last.
Let's go, Sabo.
You've been gone quite some time.
On second thought, don't come in yet.
You must be filthy.
Hose yourself off in the yard first, then come in and take a bath.
We're all glad that you're back home safe, young master.
Oh, goodness!
Is it really you?
You've grown so big.
Hello, Mom.
Now, Steli, say hello to your brother, Sabo.
Nice to meet you, big brother.
I'm Steli and I'm eight.
What about you?
What the hell?
We adopted him.
He's a promising boy from another noble family.
For reasons beyond understanding, his parents suddenly became neglectful.
So far, he's fit in extremely well.
I imagine that if things don't work out with you when it's time to choose a successor, then he would...
No, no, never mind.
I've said too much.
Go and get settled in your room.
You'll resume your studies tomorrow morning.
Are you gonna abandon all your dreams just like that?
Hey, do you know what I heard?
You're dumb as a brick.
That's what Mama and Papa think, in case you couldn't guess.
But still, you sure are lucky.
Tomorrow night, they're taking care of the garbage.
To think had you stayed in Grey Terminal a day longer, you'd be dead like the rest of the crooks.
Too bad.
My life would be a lot easier if you never came back, but I'm clever enough so I'll make do.
Heyo, stop! Let go of me or I'll tell Papa!
What did you say? What's going on?
You tell me everything, or I'll beat you up.
Wait! Tomorrow, there's going to be a fire!
They're burning Grey Terminal!
A fire?
That's right!
You didn't hear about it because you've been away for so long.
The nobles in Hightown decided it months ago.
The world government is sending a group of people to check out all of the East Blue.
They're finally going to arrive and go a kingdom three days from now.
Rumor has it they have a world noble, a celestial dragon with them.
People are panicking. The members of the royal family don't want him to see all the dirty parts of this country.
So they made the obvious decision to burn down Grey Terminal.
It's a surefire way to cleanse this country of all its rubbish.
There's no way they'd just burn everything down without warning!
Don't joke about something like that!
There's a lot of people living in Grey Terminal.
They can't just torch down their homes because they feel like it!
Get off of me!
You really are stupid. Haven't you heard a single thing I've said?
All the shame of this country. Tomorrow they're gonna burn it all away.
The people... too?
Hey! Wait up!
Where are you going?
You can't jump out the window like that!
Wow! He's a goner!
It's a lie! It's gotta be!
They can't burn down a place that big!
And someone would've heard!
Soldiers from this afternoon...
Are we sure we're ready for tomorrow?
There can't be any miscalculations!
We're ready on our end, but we're stuck relying on the pirates.
They have to burn the trash precisely at the right time!
Don't worry! Blue Jam and his men have been placing boxes of oil and explosives all over Grey Terminal.
Just like we asked.
Blue Jam has a hand in this? It must be true!
But why? What's in it for him?
Hey Ace! What do you think Saba's doing?
Seriously? Shut up!
I thought we had agreed to stop worrying about him for now.
Okay...
Who knows? This could actually work out better for him.
Saba...
Hey Luffy!
Where's my telescope?
My telescope...
Okay, think.
If there was really going to be a fire tonight,
the people in the town would be upset about it, right?
Why, good morning.
A good morning to you, sir.
What a beautiful sunny day.
Yes, lovely.
What a relief.
Guess there's nothing fishy happening today after all.
I'll walk around for a bit.
And just wait.
Come tomorrow morning, things will be nicer than ever before.
Yes, it'll be wonderful.
It's a little breezy, but everything else here seems as normal as can be.
Today is windy.
That's true, your majesty. Very windy indeed.
Accidents can happen easily on a day like this, especially wildfires.
How right you are, majesty. It's quite possible.
What? Sabo snuck out of the house?
He's such an ungrateful brat.
All he cares about is playing pirate with his friends when he should stay at home and study.
Have the police search the entire town.
He couldn't have gotten very far by himself.
Um, excuse me.
What do you want, kid?
Did you know that there's supposed to be a fire in Great Terminal tonight?
Of course I know about the fire.
Why, what's wrong? Did they cancel it?
He knows.
Tell me, boy, whose family are you from?
So, it's true.
Hold on!
Everyone knows, don't they? They have from the start!
Look at them! They're smiling!
They don't give a damn about the people in Great Terminal!
They're happy to see them burned to the ground!
You know, we've been waiting on you.
Are there any more boxes you need us to move?
Yeah, and I've got a bigger job for you later on.
But we'll talk more about that tonight.
Dad knows about it, too.
Crap.
That's why he brought me back home when he did.
As much as he hates me,
he still needs someone to inherit his property
and maintain the family's reputation.
Oh, sorry about that.
He gets excited around new faces.
Sounds to me like you're out of breath.
Is there something bothering you?
No, sir. It's nothing.
Is that so?
All right, then.
Say, I was wondering.
Did you know that there's supposed to be a fire going on in Great Terminal tonight?
Yes, I heard all about the fire.
And you're not worried? At all?
Nobody in this town cares what happens?
Nobody in town even thinks of stopping this thing?
Hmm.
That's admirable love you. You must have a very kind heart.
But boy, please don't you say a word.
It's important that we all keep our mouths shut.
Think, what would happen if someone outside of Hightown found out about the plan?
You and I are special. We come from great noble families.
Calm down.
Ace. Luffy. There's something wrong with this town.
Something wrong with these people.
They know people are going to die. They're happy people are going to die. They're sick. This whole place is sick. I can't stay here any longer. I have to tell them right now.
Today of all days. Why is it so windy?
That's him. That's the missing boy.
Excuse me, kid. You need to come with us.
Hey, you. Stop running.
The nobles here don't care who they kill. They'll burn a whole town alive just because they don't like it.
You've got to get out of Great Terminal and you've got to get out now.
Hold on, Ace! Luffy! I'm coming!
Luffy and Ace unwittingly aided Blue Jam in the plan to burn down Great Terminal and may now perish themselves.
However, when Blue Jam runs into troubles of his own, the night descends into chaos. As the flames reach higher and higher, Sabo struggles in vain to save his friends.
On the next, One Piece! The fire has been set! The Great Terminal in crisis! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!